Why are they here?
This is the only thing
I can do...
to protect all of you.
The syndicate is doing
everything to find you.
Where are you hiding now, Joey.
Are you okay, Hon?
You seem affected by the news.
Don't talk like that.
I trusted you
and you betrayed me?
You know that your life
is in danger.
We need to get rid of the pests
in our organization.
Jin Ho, what are you doing?
I got thirsty.
I'll cook.
I'll be the one
to prepare lunch.
- I'll do it.
- This is what I want.
Thank you,
because you thought of me
when I wasn't feeling well.
Wait here.
I'll just talk to these three.
Follow me!
[OBB]
What? You think I did not notice
that you're making moves
on my daughter?
[LIGHT PLAYFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
You're even sucking up to me!
Sorry, Sir.
Don't play dumb!
I know you understand me!
Uncle Miguel,
you're angry with me too?
Joey isn't feeling well,
I'm just trying to cheer her up.
Your style is rotten!
You're just starting,
I've already been there.
Ah, because you used to do that,
Uncle...
Ah, Major, you used to do that?
Yes, but I stay in my lane.
You might be forgetting.
We're here hiding
from the syndicate.
Behave yourselves, okay?
[LIGHT PLAYFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
I'm on my way.
Just make sure
nothing happens to me.
Please guarantee my protection.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
Don't worry, Liza,
I will take care of you.
Chief is trying to call
Major Delgado.
It would be better
if we meet now.
I'm leaving now.
[OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
What's your problem?
You're ruining my plan!
Well, I'm just trying
to patch things up with Joey.
I hurt her.
Now, I'm trying
to make it up to her.
You guys!
No take backs!
You let your chance pass!
He's right!
You should give chance
to others.
- [CHUCKLES]
- Give chance to others?
You too? I thought
there was a bro code?
What happened to that?
[LIGHT PLAYFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Like you?
You know what?
All is fair in love and war.
Ah, so that's it...
you want war...
Okay, I am in!
Oh, come on!
Love and war, huh.
If that's the case,
then I am in!
- Oh, come on!
- [SPLASHES]
You guys need to cool down, huh!
You're a traitor, Oppa!
What?
Survival of the fittest, huh!
You think so.
[GROWLS]
Dad, will they be okay there?
Let them be.
They look like they're enjoying.
- [GRUNTING]
- Hey, hey!
Hey, can you stop?
Can you stop?
Can you stop, please?
- Enough!
- [GRUNTING]
Come on.
It's cold.
You should rest.
[PLEASANT MUSIC PLAYING]
What happened there?
Ah, ignore them.
- Let's just talk!
- Oppa!
Come on, come on, come on!
Come on!
- [YELPS]
- [SPLASHES]
[CAR HORN BLARING]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
You're blocking my way.
Where are you going again?
None of your business.
I didn't get any memo to ask
permission from you, did I?
[GRUNTS]
[SPITS]
- What's wrong with you?
- Oh, enough, enough!
[SPLASHING]
Enough! I surrender!
I surrender.
You surrender, so...
Okay, I win.
What?
[PLAYFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
You said you surrender.
[CHUCKLES]
You wish.
What do you mean you wish?
What's your problem?
You already have Liza, right?
Why are you interfering?
Exactly!
Yes, you're just hurting Joey!
That's true!
Okay, that was then.
Okay? I admit I hurt her.
But now, I'm fixing it,
and I'm trying to make it work.
Okay?
- Wait, why you?
- What?
I'm Joey's friend,
so I have the biggest chance.
Right, you're her friend.
You're her friend,
and then what?
Your face is back on TV again.
Do you know that?
That means if someone sees you,
it's another problem!
Fine!
If you don't want me to go out,
you buy what I need.
I need wet wipes, napkin,
and feminine wash,
and I need it now.
You should also park my car,
okay?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Okay, guys.
[PLAYFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
- Oh, fine.
- Okay?
Gentleman's agreement, okay?
Whoever Joey chooses,
that's final!
No one else meddle.
If she chooses me,
don't intrude.
Okay, fine!
Fine! Fine!
[SPLASHING]
You're so annoying.
Hey!
You know, Joey...
I have this fear
that I'll lose you someday.
Dad, why?
Do we have enemies here?
[PLEASANT MUSIC PLAYING]
Yes.
Those three eggs.
They are my enemies.
Joey, I know...
the day will come...
you'll be separated
from me and your mother.
You'll find someone you love.
You'll have your own family.
You know, no matter
how much I prepare.
When that day comes, surely...
surely, I'll be hurt.
Dad, where did that come from?
Why are you suddenly
saying that?
Ah, someone...
Someone reminded me...
I know that day will come.
Dad, that's still
a long time away, okay?
I know it's a long time away,
but that day will come.
And I hope
when that day comes...
you'll find the man who will
love and care for you.
That's me, I know.
Like what you did for mom.
That's why I think
when I find a man for me,
of course, I want
someone like you, loving,
brave...
resourceful, clever.
That's me too.
That's me too, I know.
and principled.
But it's hard to find someone
like you, Dad.
So, what now?
I think you'll have
a hard time too.
So good luck to you.
[CHUCKLES]
But you know, Joey...
I hope you'll be happy.
And remember,
your mother and I are here
whenever you need us.
I'll make sure, Dad,
that I'll choose the right man,
and you'll be happy for me.
I want someone...
as loving as you
and as handsome.
There, you'll have
a hard time there.
Yes! Love you!
[PLEASANT MUSIC CONTINUES]
It's one of us three.
Hey!
[PLAYFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
What are you doing here?
Ah, looking for eggs.
Ah, nothing.
Ah, we're cleaning.
Good night, good night!
Good night, Joey!
Good night! Good night!
[PLAYFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
Go rest now, Joey.
Good night, Dad.
I love you.
Love you.
What? You woke up early.
They woke up earlier.
Huh?
[PLEASANT MUSIC PLAYING]
Wow, wow...
Okay, just relax.
You can do it.
- Oh...
- Oh.
Release the brake a little.
- There, there.
- Okay, there.
- Whoo!
- There, there, okay.
- Don't let go.
- I won't let go.
See, I can do it.
- Oh, oh, oh, oh...
- Hey, hey, hey, hey!
I might fall!
No, no, no, no!
Ouch! Whoo...
Sorry.
I got nervous.
But in fairness, I can do it.
Yes.
Wait, ah...
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
- Good thing...
- I have something to say.
Oh, you have something to say?
Ah, you, you go first.
Ah, I just want to say...
Good thing we're okay now.
Actually, I thought about
what you said.
It's true.
We're not really meant
for each other.
Because you're such
a serious person.
I don't even know
if you can smile.
You're mature already.
Old, like that?
Not really, I mean...
Because me, I still have a lot
to experience
and want to do.
[SENTIMENTAL MUSIC PLAYING]
I don't even know
how to ride a bike.
That's why I'll teach you.
I'll teach you like...
This, biking.
Because...
that's how it is, right?
When you're friends,
you help each other.
That's why I hope
we can help Jin Ho too.
For me, that's what I want,
that no matter what happens,
the four of us will
still have a solid friendship.
Okay.
Ah...
You also had something to say,
right?
Ah...
Nothing.
- Nothing.
- Are you sure?
Yes, come on,
let's go biking.
Okay.
- Hey!
- Slowly.
Hey!
Had I known,
I would've woken up earlier.
[SIGHS]
Early bird gets the worm,
really.
But the second mouse
gets the cheese.
What? What does that mean?
[PLAYFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
We'll see.
Hey...
Let's do it again next time.
So, was biking okay, Joey?
Oh, honestly, I still felt
a bit awkward.
A little more practice.
But the one teaching me
is really good.
Yes.
That's right.
Oh, were you saying something?
[PLEASANT MUSIC PLAYING]
Ah, yes.
Actually, once I learn
how to bike,
maybe he can teach me to ride a
motorcycle!
- What?
- Yes.
Okay, I'll return this now.
- Can you do it?
- I can now.
You're old.
- Hey.
- Oh!
- Snake! Snake!
- Where? Where?
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
[CHUCKLES]
- Whoa!
- Hey!
- That got me.
- Why us?
He's mad, look.
Prank lang 'yun!
- Prank...
- OA.
I am just kidding.
Goodbye!
Take care!
[JOEY CHUCKLES]
Hey, say sorry!
- Say sorry.
- Say sorry!
[PLEASANT MUSIC CONTINUES]
This is where we'll bond!
Jin Ho, Peter!
Come on, hurry!
- Joey!
- Hey!
- Amazing!
What a nice place!
Wow, Joey's really good
at finding spots.
No, it's me.
Come on, I just found
a nice spot,
- you're overdoing the praise.
- Yes!
[PETER SNIFFING]
- Wow...
- Let's eat.
- Right now?
- Yes.
Do you want?
No, I'll wait for the drinks.
Ah, drinks.
[PLAYFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
- For you.
- For me?
Thank you.
It's delicious.
-So, are you going to the beach?
- Ah, let's eat.
Guys, guys, oh!
- This is for you.
- There!
It's really for you.
Actually, two for you.
- Yes. That's so nice.
- It's destiny.
- Very nice, thank you.
- We're, you know, friends.
Thank you.
- Thank you, Brother.
- Yes.
Guys, you have two, okay.
Enjoy!
For us, just one.
- Oh, thank you.
- Joey.
[PLAYFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
You know, we should
all be careful here.
There might be, you know,
insects like...
Scary insects like...
- Maybe bees, right?
- Ah...
And, you know,
like wild animals, right.
Like...
Snake! Snake! Snake!
[SCREAMING]
Oh, so you're good
at pranks too.
What do you think of me?
Old?
- Ah, you're not?
- No.
Oh, oh, oh.
Don't get mad, okay?
You started it, right?
Okay, okay, we'll let you
off this time.
- We're even now, okay?
- Okay, fine.
- We're even.
- Is this a snake?
- What?
Yeah.
[PLAYFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Yuck.
- Yuck.
- [CHUCKLES]
- Here.
- You can do it!
Ah...
Snake, snake!
Nice.
- Snake.
- [CHUCKLES]
Cheers!
- Cheers!
Oh...
What is that for?
Well, of course, to celebrate
our friendship.
I hope it's always like this,
no problems.
Yes, we all wish that.
[PLEASANT MUSIC PLAYING]
That's right.
We don't really know
what will happen,
especially to Jin Ho.
Oh, why do you all look sad
suddenly?
You know, whatever we're going
through,
we should still think
of being happy.
Like me now, I'm happy...
because I'm with
the most handsome,
most hardworking,
most intelligent,
and cool friends.
But you know, I'm really
grateful to you
because whatever I tell you,
I feel safe.
I can trust you.
My boy friends.
Oh!
Me? Boyfriend?
[PLEASANT MUSIC PLAYING]
Boy friends.
because you're all boys
and you're all my friends.
- Ah...
- Boy friends.
Oh, do you get it?
- Friends...
- Okay.
- Cheers?
- Cheers!
To Joey's boy friends.
[PLEASANT MUSIC CONTINUES]
[CHUCKLING]
Liza!
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[PHONE CHIMES]
If you help us, we'll help you.
Come over later.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
What are you doing here?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
I've been here for a while.
I brought the new effects.
I was also with
one of our suppliers.
Where did you come from?
There you go again.
If you're really curious,
the evidence is in the bathroom,
still red.
Anyway, I'll go
to the supplier now.
Move aside.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[PHONE RINGS]
Did the supplier arrive?
Yes, Berdugo.
But we have one problem.
What is it this time?
The one you asked me to watch
seems to be planning something.
If she tries,
I'll kill her myself.
"Kill her?"
What do you mean?
[FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING]
You're going to kill someone?
It was just an expression.
To be honest, I just got pissed
at my man.
What did she do this time
to merit murder?
It doesn't matter.
Tomas, be careful
with what you say.
What if the kids
or other people hear you?
What will they think?
Can you just let it go?
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
And don't you ever dictate
how I should speak!
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
I hope you're right, Jin Ho.
What do you mean you are
changing your mind?
You don't want to stay
in this organization anymore?
Yes, you heard me.
I'm done, Liza.
We said it before...
we get enough money...
- then we disappear.
- Disappear?
This is our life, Jin Ho.
You can't just walk away
from that.
Look what we have here.
We have money, we have power,
we have protection.
And what? You just want
to trade that with peace?
Peace is overrated.
This life will kill us.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[CREAKING]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[CAR REVVING]
- [TIRES SCREECHING]
- [SCREAMS]
[CRASHES]
Ah, Chief, what happened
to Cruz's contact?
For the second time,
he didn't show up.
He tried calling
but couldn't reach him.
The caller's location
can't be traced anymore.
Maybe the phone is off.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
Maybe that contact
was just messing around.
And the info he gave,
maybe it wasn't true.
I don't think so.
We have a strong feeling
he wasn't lying.
Chief, did Cruz identify
who called the hotline?
Liza De Leon.
[BRAZEN MUSIC PLAYING]
[OSTRICH CLUCKINPG]
Good morning, Joey.
[PLEASANT MUSIC PLAYING]
Good morning.
I wanted to feed them.
But they won't come near.
Ah, them?
[OSTRICH CLUCKINPG]
Okay, I'll help you.
Jin Ho!
[CLICKS TONGUE]
Peter!
Come here!
[CLICKS TONGUE]
Jin Ho!
No use, they're stubborn.
I can do it.
Ah, Andrew...
About what I said to you
before...
Forget it, okay?
I also thought it's better
if we just stay friends.
That's exactly
what I don't want...
to just be friends.
Why? Did I say something?
Did I do something?
Actually, yes, Joey.
I don't know when,
I don't know where...
But, Joey, there is.
I'm sure about
how I feel for you.
I love you, Joey.
[DREAMY MUSIC PLAYING]
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
What's happening, Dad?
Liza was supposed to surrender.
But, she didn't show up.
Something bad
must have happened to her.
I want to help you
fight Berdugo.
I've been through so much
with this person.
I want to be the one
to catch him myself.
He's doing it for Liza.
Because if you love someone,
you're willing to take a risk.
Do you really have to talk to
him like that?
Do you and Joey have a problem?
Is Jin Ho still asleep?
He's not in his room either.
Then where is he?
The Korean escaped.
He even took my gun.
We need to get even.
I'll take care of it, Berdugo.
Help me!